Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A bride and groom with members of their families around them. 8.5 x 13.4 cm, 15 June [-?-]; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Brides; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Ceremony
- A group of mixed males and females seated a dinner table. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Studio Basin Foto, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Drinking; Eating; Gatherings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A young female in short dress and tan trench coat seated in a white chair. 12.5 x 8.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A young male in a dark suit and patterned pocket square. 11.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- A young male standing on a balcony in a light suit with a fedora. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young couple standing in tall grass in the countryside. 8.5 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Couple; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Maritime Outfits; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Two young females in lederhosen. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Studio Mustafa, Izmir, Turkey (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Traditional Dress
- A young couple on the dance floor, female in a pin striped skirt suit. Turkish writing on the back "The best days of my life". 8.5 x 13.3 cm, 1 May 1941; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Couple; Dancing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- Two women in bathing suits at the beach. 9.2 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Bathing Suits; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A woman in a black dress with a white flower on the front and black hat, standing in the door way of a house. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A woman in a black skirt and dark top seated on a chair in front a window sill with potted plants. 13.6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Turkey; Women
- A seated female in a light patterned dress. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
- A female leaning on a plant stand, wearing a fur lined coat and a head cover. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Coats; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Individual Portraits; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- Two young males with mustaches with a potted flower on a table between them. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- Two females in long coats standing in front of a large tree in the countryside. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, 12 March 1951; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Architecture; Coats; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young female in a light silk dress with a dark colored purse in her lap. 12.7 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Architecture; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young female in a dark winter coat with a dark hat, three tufts of hair are hanging out of the hat. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 6 July 1921; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Individual Portraits; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- Two males standing in front of some hedges and trees, one is a uniform holding a hat. 13.8 x 8.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey; Uniforms
- A young female in a dark dress, background has some special effects. 13.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
- A group of females and males surrounding a bride. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Brides; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Portraits; Women
- A group of four females in Western dress, seated female is wearing a patterned shawl. 13.3 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A group of six females surrounding a bride in a white veil. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Esen, Ankara, Turkey (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Ankara, Turkey; Gelatin Silver Prints; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils; Women
- A group of seven females, female on the left in a polka dot dress. 8.5 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young couple, female in a light dress with baubles, male in dark suit and bow tie with thick eyebrows. 13.7 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A seated female with sheer top and an older couple standing in the background. 13.1 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A group of males seated around a table near a body of water, a young female is seated at the table biting her finger. 10.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Children; Cigarettes; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Seas; Turkey
- A male with a mustache in a coat standing in front of a large tree. Duplicate photo. 13.2 x 8.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Park, Izmir, Turkey (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A family group standing in the garden of a large house with white flowers. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, 8 March 1958; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Boys; Children; Family; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- School children seated at their desks in a classroom with a teacher standing in the back. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 5 January 1960; Studio Ramiz Goksay, Izmir, Turkey (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Books; Children; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Schools; Studio Photography
- An older male in pajamas and slippers standing on a roof. 12.5 x 8.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Pajamas; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A group of older males wih paper hat seated/standing around a table. 9.2 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Cigarettes; Entertainment; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Smoking; Suits; Turkey
- A young male in a dark suit with a dark bow tie and white pocket square and a short mustache. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 7 [-?-] 1930; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
- A bride and groom are standing in front of a window in a house, bride has on a black ribbon necklace. 13.5 x 8.6 cm, 13 November 1952; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Brides; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Veils
- A female standing in a light dress with a black purse on her right arm, in front of a mirror. 13.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Ceremony; Women
- A couple, female is wearing a dark dress with a pin on the collar, male is wearing a dark suit. 9.0 x 13.5 cm, 10 October 1938; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A family group, young female in a white dress standing in the middle. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Brides; Couple; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Ceremony
- A young boy wearing a checkered jacket and white hat. 12.6 x 7.9 cm, 7 September 1939; Unknown (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young female in a dark dress with a white collar. 12.5 x 8.3 cm, 5 June 1952; Studio Foto Sabah, Adana, Turkey (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Adana, Turkey; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing
- A family group surrounding a bed with patterned cover, after a birth. 14.0 x 19.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Beds; Births; Children; Family; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey
- Three young males with mustaches, two standing, one seated with books in his lap. 30.0 x 23.9 cm, 1926; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Books; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mustaches; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- A school group, mixed boys and girls taken in front of some trees, teachers on the ends. 21.0 x 26.3 cm, 15 May 1967; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Boys; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey
- A Pasha with mustache, holding a sword. Stamp on the back. 21.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Boudoir-Portrait, Damascus, Syria; Indiveri, Francesco (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Albumen Prints; Fezes; French Writing; Individual Portraits; Men; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Swords & Knives; Syria; Traditional Dress
- A family group, female seated on chair in black dress, young male in dark short suit, younger female with large dark bow in white shirt. 23.3 x 17.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Children; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A group of four young females in dresses outdoors. Ottoman writing on front and back. 12.0 x 18.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A female in a light trench coat with a brooch, standing in front of some trees with a building in the background. 17.7 x 23.0 cm, May 1934; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Coats; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A school group of mixed males and females in uniforms, older female standing on the right. 18.0 x 23.3 cm, 1951; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Armenian Writing; Boys; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A mixed group of males and females in front of a building complex with a mosque in the background. 17.9 x 23.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Men; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A male with a short mustache and thick eyebrows wearing a dark coat. 24.5 x 18.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Coats; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A young couple. 22.8 x 24.4 cm, 15 August 1934; Studio Turk Foto Evi, R. Koro, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul University; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkish Writing
- A young male with a thick mustache wearing a dark suit with a small pocket watch on his belt. 13 Mart 1332 (1914 in Gregorian caldendar) on the back. 27.7 x 17.4 cm, 21 March 1914; Sebah & Joaillier, Pera, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Constantinople; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young male standing in front of a white fence, frame has white and pink flowers surrounding it. 27.9 x 21.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Boys; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A class at Kuleli Military School, males in full military uniform. 21.6 x 26.69 cm, 8 December 1940; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Schools; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A young couple, female in a checked coat, male in military uniform with a white hat. 22.5 x 20.0 cm, 28 October 1952; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Coats; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gloves; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- Several officials, mostly older males in suits outside a stone building, one male in a military uniform on the right side. 21.3 x 25.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Military; Officials; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A young male and young female both dressed in white. Male is wearing a white hat and a sash. 23.7 x 16.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Boys; Children; Circumcisions; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- Older males in front of a building. Backing has two pieces broken off. 21.8 x 26.8 cm, 18 December 1938; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A family group, seated female with dark head cover, two seated males in military uniform, young male in dark outfit with white collar. 13.4 x 18.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Boys; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Uniforms
- A young couple embracing in front of a wall and trees. 22.1 x 16.8 cm, 21 September 1937; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Clocks & Watches; Couple; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A young female in a light colored dress with small dark flowers on it. 23.0 x 16.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A young, married couple dancing, female in a bridal gown. 24.0 x 18.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Brides; Dancing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Veils
- A married couple is standing on a parquette floor platform. 23.9 x 17.9 cm, Undated; Studio Artistik, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Brides; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils
- A young seated female in a dark dress with large dark bow. 29.3 x 18.4 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Rekor, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A small family group, seated older female and male, two standing young males in suits and one standing female in a light dress. 19.4 x 28.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- A small family group, seated older male and female, one standing male in suit and two standing females in dresses. 28.5 x 18.5 cm, 12 August 1934; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Family Portraits; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A group males in uniform outside a stone building with white barred windows. 21.8 x 27.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Uniforms
- A mixed group of females in dress and males in suits and uniforms in front of large columns. "People of Isparta in Istanbul" 24.8 x 21.1 cm, 16 March 1941; Studio Foto Sadi, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Uniforms; Women
- A group of males of varying ages, Arabic numbers in blue ink. 19.5 x 27.9 cm, 17 [-?-] 1928; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Military; Ottoman Writing; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Uniforms
- A group of four in the countryside with mountains and houses in the background. 21.6 x 26.5 cm, 3 May 1939; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Countryside; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Uniforms; Women
- An older covered woman. 30.5 x 24.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A group of men, one woman and a dog seated around an outdoor table. 16.5 x 21.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Dogs; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parks; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey
- A family group with two women seated in the front with the same dress on. 24.1 x 19.1 cm, 19 October 1932; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Family; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- A young male soldier in uniform, side profile. Turkish writing on the back. 23.7 x 17.5 cm, 3 April 1934; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey
- A young female in a light patterned dress holding a young child in a white outfit. 24.3 x 18.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Children; Clocks & Watches; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A young male soldier in military uniform with hat. 25.0 x 20.4 cm, Undated; Studio Nuri Hamza Rustem Fotografhanesi, Izmir, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Izmir, Turkey; Military; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Uniforms
- A couple dressed in dark outfits with young girl in white outfit with black shoes. 26.9 x 22.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Bow Ties; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Jewelry; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- A family group of five, with a dark haired dog. 26.7 x 21.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Dogs; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey
- A bride and groom standing on stone steps with two male youths and female youth in the background. 27.8 x 20.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Architecture; Brides; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey; Wedding Veils
- A seated female with long hair in a dark dress. 27.9 x 20.5 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Aile, Kadikoy, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Handtinting; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Women
- A class of young males with older male teacher in front of an old stone wall with trees and buildings in the background. 21.8 x 27.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Boys; Countryside; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Suits; Turkey
- A family group, two young girls are seated with matching bows, small eagle embossed in the upper left corner of the backing. 22.8 x 27.7 cm, Undated; Studio Photo L'Aigle, Grand Rue de Pera 429, Constantinople (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Constantinople; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Head Covers; Istanbul, Turkey; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young male in a pinstripped suit and patterned bow tie, side profile. 29.7 x 19.0 cm, 15 August 1938; Studio Foto Rekor, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Bow Ties; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkish Writing
- An old man with a beard seated on a light cushion in the countryside with a jug and a pair of shoes in front of him. 23.2 x 28.3 cm, 26 August 1942; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Countryside; Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- Seljuk Caravanserai in Anatolia. Ottoman script embossed in backing. Intricate red stamp with Ottoman script on the back. 27.9 x 22.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Anatolia, Turkey; Archaeological Sites; Architecture; Caravanserai; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A woman in a black dress with a detailed lace collar. 29.5 x 22.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 22)
- A couple, male holding a cane, female wearing a light shirt with a dark bow. 31.7 x 24.7 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Yurt, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Clocks & Watches; Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A group portrait of men and women indoors. Signatures on the reverse. 31.4 x 26.4 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Evi, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- An older couple, female is wearing a dark dress with a pearl necklace with a coin on it. 32.7 x 26.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Mustaches; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A school group of young boys and girls in front of some buildings. 26.3 x 32.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 22)
- A young male in a dark suit with dark rimmed glasses. 32.7 x 26.2 cm, 21 January 1963; Studio Foto Izmir, Ankara, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Ankara, Turkey; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- Men in military uniform with drafting books seated on a grassy hilltop. 26.8 x 33.0 cm, 1926; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Countryside; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Military; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Turkey; Uniforms
- A school group of young males in uniform in front of a building with barred windows. 27.9 x 33.5 cm, 1931; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Armenian Writing; Boys; Education; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Schools; Studio Photography; Turkey; Uniforms
- A bride and groom standing in front several large flower arrangements. 33.5 x 27.6 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sehir, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Brides; Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Grooms; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veils
- A group of young male and female doctors and nurses in uniforms standing in front of a building with a fenced portico. Turkish writing on the back: "To Dr. Cahide, a souvenir from the group of gynocology interns". 28.4 x 33.5 cm, 28 February 1945; Studio Foto Sehir, Turkey (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Doctors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Medicine; Nurses; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey; Turkish Writing
- An older covered female. Turkish writing on the back. 32.3 x 26.5 cm, 1 September 1953; Unknown (Box 2, Folder 24)